Guide to the Atlantic Philanthropies Archives, 1982-2017.
Atlantic Philanthropies Archives,
- Series IV: Grant Files
  - Subseries E: Great Britian grant files, 1974-2011
    - Robinson CollegeUniversity of Cambridge, 1998-2005; Robinson College (University of Cambridge); University of Cambridge
      - #7919 (#99-124). Core support, 2001-2004 (Box 199, Folder 3)
        Dublin office cabinet file Cab. 1, Dr. 1, 36/10
    - Roundhouse Trust, 2000-2006
      Roundhouse (London, England)
      - #10589. The Roundhouse Creative Centre. Key documents, 2000-2005 (Box 199, Folder 4)
        Arts Programs and Services
      - #10589. The Roundhouse Creative Centre. Final report, 2005-2006 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - Royal School for Deaf Children, 1994-1999; Royal School for Deaf Children (Margate, England)
      Royal School for Deaf Children (Margate, England)
      - #7257 (#94-28) and #7917 (#99-123). Core support and Children's library, 1994, 1996, 1999 (Box 199, Folder 6)
        Special Education
        E-Learning
        School Libraries and Media Centers
        Hearing Care
    - Scottish Community Foundation, 2000-2004
      Scottish Community Foundation
      - #9741. Strategic intervention fund, 2001-2004 (Box 199, Folder 7)
        Neighborhood Associations
      - #9741. Strategic intervention fund. Key documents, 2001-2004 (Box 199, Folder 8)
      - Reports and supplemental materials, 2000-2004 (Box 199, Folder 9-12)
        - The State Street Caledonian challenge: in support of the Scottish Community Foundation: CD-ROM postcard, 2003; CD-5392 (Box 199, Folder 11)
          Contains a 20 minute video of the 2003 Caledonian Challenge, plus a 15 minute training presentation
          CD-ROM
    - Scottish Council for Voluntary Organisations (SCVO), 1984-2006; Scottish Council for Voluntary Organisations
      Scottish Council for Voluntary Organisations
      - #8990. Technical team/web development, 2001, 2003 (Box 199, Folder 13)
      - #8990. Technical team/web development. Annual review 2002-03 and key documents, 2001-2004 (Box 199, Folder 14)
      - #10886. Understanding the voluntary sector in rural Scotland. Rural development, 2001-2006 (Box 199, Folder 15-16)
        N 19/18
      - Supplemental material, 1984, 1994, 1999-2004 (Box 199, Folder 17-18)
        Folders contains materials such as proposals, reviews, reports, and publications.
        - APIO (from SCVO), FD-950 (Box 199, Folder 18)
    - Scottish Human Services Trust (SHS), 2001-2005; Scottish Human Services Trust
      Scottish Human Services Trust
      - #10057. Strengthening the core of the Scottish Human Services Trust, 2001-2003 (Box 199, Folder 19)
        Family Services
        Housing and Shelter Services
        Family Disability Resources
      - #10057. Strengthening the core of the Scottish Human Services Trust, 2001, 2005 (Box 199, Folder 20)
    - Solas Anois, 1994-1997
      Solas Anois
      - #7314 (#95-23). Core support, 1994-1997 (Box 199, Folder 21)
    - Solicitors Pro Bono Group, 1999-2001; LawWorks (Charity)
      LawWorks (Charity)
      - #7909 (#99-117). Feasibility study, 1999 (Box 199, Folder 22)
      - #8409. Lawyers' Alliance for London pilot project, 2001 (Box 199, Folder 23)
        Legal Services
      - #8409. Lawyer's Alliance for London pilot project. Key documents, 1999, 2001 (Box 199, Folder 24)
    - Southall Black Sisters Trust, 2001-2003; Southall Black Sisters (Group)
      Southall Black Sisters (Group)
      - #9461; #12096. The National Policy and Good Practice Project on Black/Minority Women and Sexual/Gender Violence; Documentary film on gender violence, 2001, 2003 (Box 199, Folder 25)
        Freedom from Violence/Torture
      - #9461. The national policy and good practice project on black/minority women and sexual/gender violence. Key documents, 2001, 2003 (Box 199, Folder 26)
      - #12096. Documentary film on gender violence. Key documents, 2003 (Box 199, Folder 27)
    - St. Gabriel's Community Assisted Home, 1990-1993
      St. Gabriel's Community Assisted Home
      - #7015 (#90-2). Core support, 1990-1993 (Box 199, Folder 28)
        No GRS included
        Health Facilities
    - St. George in-the-East Trust, 1992-1993
      St. George-in-the-East (Church: London, England)
      - #7126 (#92-24). Research report, 1992-1993 (Box 199, Folder 29)
    - Tim Parry Johnathan Ball Trust, 1998-2006; Tim Parry Johnathan Ball Foundation for Peace
      Tim Parry Johnathan Ball Foundation for Peace
      - #7825 (#99-34) and #10890. Tim Parry Johnathan Ball Young People's Centre at Warrington, 1998-1999, 2003-2004 (Box 199, Folder 30)
        Group Homes
      - #10890. The Warrington Peace Center, 2000-2006 (Box 199, Folder 31-32)
        N 17/52/1
    - Trinity College of Music Trust, 1996-2005
      Trinity College of Music
      - #7588 (#97-115) Feasibility study for relocation to Greenwich., 1997, 2002 (Box 199, Folder 33)
        Dublin office cabinet file (36/5/1)
      - #7779 (#98-149). Planning on relocation to Greenwich, 1998-1999 (Box 199, Folder 34)
      - #7906. Bursary fund and research program, 1999, 2001-2002 (Box 199, Folder 35)
        Dublin office cabinet file (36/5/3)
      - #9293. Database marketing and promotion project, 2001-2002, 2004 (Box 199, Folder 36)
      - #9293. Database marketing and promotion project. Key documents, 2001, 2004 (Box 199, Folder 37)
      - #9293. Database marketing and promotion project. Supplemental materials, 2000-2003 (Box 200, Folder 1)
      - #9309. Instrument fund, 2001 (Box 200, Folder 2)
        Dublin office cabinet file (36/5/4); Grant number does not appear in Fluxx
      - #9309. Instrument fund, 2001 (Box 200, Folder 3)
        Grant number does not appear in Fluxx
      - #9309. Instrument fund. Key documents, 2001-2002 (Box 200, Folder 4)
      - #9634. Orchestral practice facility, 2001-2003 (Box 200, Folder 5)
        Orchestras
      - #9634. Orchestral practice facility. Key documents, 2001-2003 (Box 200, Folder 6)
      - #11834. Blackheath Halls, 2003-2005 (Box 200, Folder 7)
        Dublin office cabinet file Cab 1. Dr. 1, 36/5/7
      - #11834. Blackheath Halls. Key documents, 2003-2004 (Box 200, Folder 8)
      - Feasibility study for relocation to Greenwich / Music education in schools, 1996-1998 (Box 200, Folder 9)
        Dublin office cabinet file 36/5
    - University College London (UCL), 1997-2006; University College, London
      University College, London
      - #7948 (#99-153.) School of Public Policy, 1997-2002 (Box 200, Folder 10-11)
        Dublin office cabinet file Cab. 1, Dr. 1, 36/9/1
        University College, London. School of Public Policy
      - #9637. Widening participation, 2001-2004 (Box 200, Folder 12)
      - #9637. Project to widen college attendance for under-represented groups. Key documents, 2001-2004 (Box 200, Folder 13)
      - #10009. Cancer Institute. Key documents, 1999-2002 (Box 200, Folder 14)
        Includes: oversized floor plans
      - #10009. Cancer Institute, 2001-2003, 2006 (Box 200, Folder 15)
        Dublin office cabinet file Cab. 1, Dr. 36/9/2
      - University College London, 2001 (Box 200, Folder 16)
        Dublin office cabinet file 36/9
    - University of Brighton, 2002-2004
      University of Brighton
      - #10912. Community-University Partnership Project. Key documents, 2002-2004 (Box 200, Folder 17)
    - University of Liverpool, 1992-2005
      University of Liverpool
      - #7175 (#93-8). Institute of Irish Studies: development campaign, 1992-1997, 2000-2001 (Box 200, Folder 18)
        University of Liverpool. Institute of Irish Studies
      - #7694 (#98-61). Strategic planning. Charity Law Unit (ULCLU), 1998 (Box 200, Folder 19)
        (N 18/15) Contains only GRS and brief correspondence
        University of Liverpool. Charity Law Unit
        Law Education
        Philanthropy
      - #7694. Strategic planning. Charity Law Unit, 1994-2005 (Box 200, Folder 20-21)
      - #7694. Charity Law Unit. Key documents, 1998-2002 (Box 200, Folder 22)
      - #10310. Fundraising feasibility study. Key documents, 2002 (Box 200, Folder 23)
        fax of GRS only
      - #11222. Interim support while raising endowment for Chair of Irish Studies. Key documents, 2003 (Box 200, Folder 24)
        International Studies
    - University of the Highlands and Islands Millenium Institute, 2001-2006; University of the Highlands and Islands
      University of the Highlands and Islands
      - #12343. Youth Leadership Project, 1998, 2001-2006 (Box 200, Folder 25-26)
        N 19/19
    - VoiceVoice for the Child in Care (VCC), 2000-2006; Voice for the Child in Care (Organization)
      Voice for the Child in Care (Organization)
      - #10055. Blueprint for a child-centered care system, 1995, 2000-2004 (Box 200, Folder 27-28)
        (N 14/25); Some pages with partial tearing and adhesive
        Children's Rights
        Child Care
      - #12967. Blueprint implementation project, 2001, 2004-2006 (Box 200, Folder 29)
        N 27/8/8
        Children's Services (General)
      - Blueprint implementation, 2004-2005 (Box 200, Folder 30)
    - Wales Council for Voluntary Action (WCVA), 2000-2005; Wales Council for Voluntary Action
      Wales Council for Voluntary Action
      - #8692. The voluntary sector's impact on policy development and implementation in the new Wales, 2001, 2005 (Box 200, Folder 31)
      - #8692. The Voluntary Sector's impact on policy development and implementation in the new Wales. Key documents, 2001-2002, 2004 (Box 200, Folder 32)
      - #8692. The Voluntary Sector's impact on policy development and implementation in the new Wales. Supplemental materials, correspondence, etc., 2000-2005 (Box 200, Folder 33-34)
    - Wales Funders Forum, 1998-2005
      Wales Funders Forum
      - #9523. Investment in the new millennium, 2001 (Box 200, Folder 35)
      - #9523. Investment in the new millennium. Key documents, 2001-2004 (Box 200, Folder 36)
      - #9523. Investment in the new millennium. Reports, 2001-2005 (Box 201, Folder 1-5)
      - #9523. Investment in the new millennium. Proposal and background materials, 1998, 2000-2003 (Box 201, Folder 6-7)
        - INM bid proposal. Wales Funders Forum. July 2001, 2001-07; FD-951 (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - Women's Aid Federation of England (WAFE), 1996-2001; Women's Aid Federation of England
      Women's Aid Federation of England
      - #7927 (#99-132). Research project, 1996-2001 (Box 201, Folder 8)
        Sexual Abuse
        Child Abuse
    - Works Trust, 1998-2005
      Works Trust
      - #10273. Stockton Brook - loan forgiveness. Key documents, 1998-2000, 2002-2005 (Box 201, Folder 9)
    - World Memorial Fund for Disaster Relief, 1993-1995
      World Memorial Fund for Disaster Relief
      - #7186 (#93-20). Core funding, 1993-1994 (Box 201, Folder 10)
      - #7271 (#94-42). Core funding, 1994-1995 (Box 201, Folder 11)
    - Zero Tolerance Charitable Trust, 1994-2003; Zero Tolerance (Charity: Scotland)
      Zero Tolerance (Charity: Scotland)
      - #7614 (#97-141); #8848. Core costs/program costs, 1997-2001, 2003 (Box 201, Folder 12)
      - #8448. Zero Tolerance '96 and '97 Core support. Gift ref: 97-141. File ref: N20/4, 1994, 1996-1997 (Box 201, Folder 13)
      - #8448. Core support, 1999-2001, 2003 (Box 201, Folder 14)
      - #8448. Core support Gift ref: 97-141, Ref.: N20/4, 1997-2000 (Box 201, Folder 15-16)
      - The Zero Tolerance Charitable Trust. Core costs, 2000-11-30 (Box 201, Folder 17)
        Dublin office cabinet file Cab. 7, Dr. 1B 9/2/6/3/1
  - Subseries F: Northern Ireland grant files, 1977-2018
    Files for grants made by Atlantic Philanthropies in Northern Ireland between 1991 and 2014.
    Subseries arranged alphabetically into subseries by grantee name (as identified on FLUXX).
    Northern Ireland
    - Access to Benefits for Older People (A2B), 2005-2009, 2012; Access to Benefits for Older People
      Access to Benefits for Older People
      Ageing
      Social Security
      Health Insurance
      - A2B coordinating committee. File 1, 2006 (Box 94, Folder 1-2)
        File number N 26/8/8/1. No grant-related documents
      - A2B coordinating committee. File 2, 2006-12 (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - BTUI coordinating committee, 2004-2006 (Box 94, Folder 4-5)
      - BTUI evaluation, 2005-2007 (Box 94, Folder 6)
        File number N 26/8/8/2. No grant-related documents
      - #14311. Access to Benefits for Older People, 2006-2008 (Box 94, Folder 7)
      - #14311. Access to Benefits for Older People, 2005-2008 (Box 94, Folder 8-10)
        File number N 26/8/27.
        - Help the Aged: Launch of Age Awareness Week. 1. BBC Newsline (evening), 2. BBC Newsline (lunch), 2007-10-01; DVD-3446 (Box 94, Folder 10)
          File number N 26/8/27
      - #14311. Access to Benefits for Older People. File 1, 2006-2012 (Box 94, Folder 11-13)
      - #14311. Access to Benefits for Older People. File 2, 2006-2012 (Box 94, Folder 14-16)
        - A2B Access to Benefits: reaping rewards for older people. Launch presentations, CD-5251 (Box 94, Folder 16)
      - #14311. Access to Benefits for Older People. Reports, 2007-2009 (Box 94, Folder 17)
        - All About A2B, 2007-2009; DVD-3447 (Box 94, Folder 17)
      - #14311. Loose reports and supplemental materials, 2006-2012 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Advice NI, 2008-2014
      Advice NI
      - #15926. Social justice website for older people. Portal, 2008-2011 (Box 95, Folder 2)
        File number N 26/8/47
      - #20350. 'Advantage' and 'Rights 4 Seniors', 2011-2014 (Box 95, Folder 3)
        File number N 26/8/72
        Geriatrics
    - Age Concern Northern Ireland, 1977, 1994, 2002-2009, 2013; Age Concern Northern Ireland (Organization)
      Age Concern Northern Ireland (Organization)
      - Age Concern, 2002-2009 (Box 95, Folder 4-5)
        File number N 26/7/1. No grant-related documents.
      - Age Concern Northern Ireland--reports, 2001-2002, 2007 (Box 95, Folder 6)
      - ACNI review, 2006-2007 (Box 95, Folder 7)
        File number N 26/7/1/1. No grant-related documents.
      - ACNI review, 2007-04-17 (Box 95, Folder 8)
      - Help the Aged, 2002-2003, 2005-2006, 2008 (Box 95, Folder 9)
        File number N 26/7/2. No grant-related documents.
      - HTA -- UK, Undated (Box 95, Folder 10)
        File number N 26/7/2/1. No grant-related documents.
      - Reports, 2007, 2013 (Box 95, Folder 11)
        File number N 26/8/35
      - #13733. Collaboration and co-location planning grant, 2005 (Box 95, Folder 12)
      - #13733. Working Together, 1977, 1994, 2002-2006 (Box 95, Folder 13)
        File number N 26/8/10
    - Age NI, 2005-2013
      Age NI
      - CAP committee, 2005-2008 (Box 95, Folder 15-16)
        File number N 26/8/11/1. No grant-related documents.
        - Interviews with Anne O'Reilly. Good Morning Ulster, V105 Lynda Bryans Show, 2007-01-10-2008; CD-5252 (Box 95, Folder 16)
          File number N 26/8/11/1
      - CAP- advisory, strategy, and operations meetings, 2007-2010 (Box 96, Folder 1-3)
      - CAP, 2010-2011 (Box 96, Folder 4)
      - #14129. Age Equality Forum and Age Awareness. CAP., 2005-2009 (Box 96, Folder 5)
        File number N 26/8/16
      - #15035. Communications for CAP Age Awareness Week, 2007-2010, 2012 (Box 96, Folder 6)
        File number N 26/8/44
      - #15584. Fit for Purpose (Modernization of regional age sector), 2006-2007, 2010-2013 (Box 96, Folder 7)
        File number N 26/8/32
      - #15584. Modernization fund, 2007-2009 (Box 96, Folder 8-9)
      - #15924. Investment and sustainability (organizational review implementation), 2007-2013 (Box 96, Folder 10-12)
      - #17104. Campaign for an effective Commissioner for Older People in Northern Ireland, 2008-2010 (Box 96, Folder 13)
        No GRS included in file.
      - #17104. Older people's commissioner, 2008-2010 (Box 96, Folder 14)
        File number N 26/8/45
      - #17516. Transition project for the new charity, 2010-2013 (Box 96, Folder 15-16)
        File number N 26/8/61
        - Age NI for Later Life., DVD-3448; Duration: 14:20 (Box 96, Folder 17)
      - #19290. Home Improvement Agency, 2010-2011 (Box 97, Folder 1)
        File number N 26/8/67
    - Age Sector Platform, 2006, 2008-2009, 2011-2012, 2014
      Age Sector Platform
      - #14328. Develop and mobilize a Northern Ireland 'Seniors' platform of and by older people, 2006-2011 (Box 97, Folder 2-4)
        File number N 26/8/33
        - Pensioners rally at Stormont, 2008-11-17; DVD-3449 (Box 97, Folder 4)
        - Executive to meet again, 2008-11-19; DVD-3450 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - #18106. Strengthen the voice of the age sector, 2012 (Box 97, Folder 5)
        File number N 26/8/85
        End of Life Care
      - #18106. Strengthening the voice of the Age Sector Platform, 2009-2014 (Box 97, Folder 6-7)
        File number N 26/8/63
    - Alzheimer's Society, Northern Ireland, 2006-2013
      Alzheimer's Society, Northern Ireland
      Dementia
      - #14320. Expand support for dementia sufferers through improving advocacy, 2006-2009 (Box 97, Folder 8-9)
        File number N 26/8/26
        Health Care Management
      - #18819. Dementia Advocacy Project. Alzheimer's II, 2009-2013 (Box 97, Folder 10-11)
        File number N 26/8/62
    - American Federation for Aging Research, 2009
      American Federation for Aging Research
      Medical Education
      Gerontology
      - #14725 (#18093). Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars Program for the Republic of Ireland and Northern Ireland, 2009 (Box 97, Folder 12)
        File number N 26/8/58. Grant number of original folder does not appear in FLUXX; #14725 corresponds with the grant.
        Archivist supplied title.
    - Arts Council of Northern Ireland, 2009-2012, 2014
      Arts Council of Northern Ireland
      Adult Peer Mentoring
      Artist's Services
      - #18094. Older People, the Arts, and Social Justice, 2009-2012, 2014 (Box 97, Folder 13-14)
        File number N 26/8/54
      - #18094. Arts and older people program, 2010 (Box 98, Folder 1)
      - #18094. Steering group meeting materials, 2010-2011 (Box 98, Folder 2)
      - #18094. Reports and newsletters, 2009, 2011 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - ASCERT, 1999, 2001-2004, 2006-2007
      ASCERT
      - #9629. Community empowerment project, 1999, 2001-2004, 2006-2007 (Box 98, Folder 4-5)
        File number N 19/16
        - Community empowerment project, FD-934 (Box 98, Folder 5)
          File number N 19/16. Envelope addressed to Hugh Logue, TARA Consultants Ltd.
    - Association of Charitable Foundations, 1997-2003, 2007, 2013-2014
      Country-wide
      - ACF NI Group, 1997-2003, 2007 (Box 98, Folder 6)
        File number N 18/11. No grant related-documents
      - #22478. Increasing involvement of UK trusts in Northern Ireland, 2013-2014 (Box 98, Folder 7)
        File number N 0/0/14
    - Barnardos NI, 2005-2014; Barnardos (Ireland)
      Barnardos (Ireland)
      Prevention and Early Intervention
      - Barnardos, 2005-2006 (Box 98, Folder 8)
        File number N 27/8/13. No grant related-documents.
      - #15153. Ready to Learn. Main grant. File 1, 2008-2010, 2012 (Box 98, Folder 9-10)
        File number N 27/8/46
      - #15153. Ready to Learn. Main grant. File 2, 2010-2011 (Box 98, Folder 11)
      - #15153. Ready to Learn. Main grant. File 3, 2010-2012 (Box 98, Folder 12)
      - #15153. Ready to Learn. Main grant. File 4, 2012-2013 (Box 98, Folder 13)
      - #15153. Ready to Learn. Main grant. File 5, 2013-2014 (Box 98, Folder 14)
      - #15855. Planning grant, 2007 (Box 98, Folder 15)
      - #15855. Planning grant, 2007-2009 (Box 98, Folder 16-17)
        File number N 27/8/27
    - Belfast Community Safety Partnership, 1990, 2007-2012
      Belfast Community Safety Partnership
      - #17485. 'Good Morning' projects to combat vulnerable older people's isolation, 1990, 2007-2011 (Box 99, Folder 1-2)
        File number N 26/8/48
      - #17485. 'Good Morning' project reports, 2010-2012 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Belfast Door Project, 2000-2001, 2003-2007
      Belfast Door Project
      - Belfast Door Project, Undated (Box 99, Folder 4)
        No grant related documents.
      - Door Outreach Project. Executive Summary, 2000-09 (Box 99, Folder 5)
      - Door Outreach Project, 1997-2000. Final Report - March 2001, 2001-03 (Box 99, Folder 6)
      - #13739. Planning grant, 2003-2007 (Box 99, Folder 7-8)
        File number N 27/8/5
      - #13739. Planning grant, 2005 (Box 99, Folder 9)
      - #15156. City center young persons building, Undated (Box 99, Folder 10)
        File number N 27/8/29.
    - Belfast Together, 1999-2002
      Belfast Together
      Promoting Rights and Protecting Reconciliation
      Community Recreation
      - #8007. Travel stipend, 1999-2002 (Box 99, Folder 11)
        File number N 19/12.
    - Below the Radar, 2009-2014; Below the Radar Films (Firm)
      Below the Radar Films (Firm)
      - #19147. Web platform and research for documentary N29/1/4, 2009-2012 (Box 99, Folder 12-13)
        File number N 0/0/5
        Outside Program Areas (Legacy)
        Conflict Resolution
        Web-Based Media
      - #22599. The Detail II - the online public purpose investigative news platform for Northern Ireland, 2011-2013 (Box 99, Folder 14)
        File number N 0/0/15
        Protecting Rights and Promoting Reconciliation
        Investigative Journalism
        Government Regulation
      - #24615. Big Data Project, 2014 (Box 99, Folder 15)
        File number N 0/0/19
    - Beth Johnson Foundation, 2008-2014
      Beth Johnson Foundation
      Cross Program/Strategic Initiatives (Legacy)
      - #20119. Promoting intergenerational cooperation and solidarity. Linking generations NI, 2010-2014 (Box 99, Folder 16-18)
        File number N 26/8/70
      - #20119. Intergenerational project, 2008-2010 (Box 99, Folder 19)
        File number N 26/8/48/1
    - Big Telly Theatre Company, 2001, 2005-2013
      Big Telly Theatre Company
      - #15684. Older people and theatre, 2001, 2005-2009, 2011 (Box 100, Folder 1-2)
        File number N 26/7/30
        - Spring Chickens, 2011; DVD-3451 (Box 100, Folder 2)
      - #15684. Spring Chickens program and final report, 2009-2010 (Box 100, Folder 3-4)
        - Appendix E. Big Telly presents Spring Chickens - the Shows, 2009-10-03; DVD-3452 (Box 100, Folder 3)
        - Appendix F. Spring Chickens Production Shots, 2009; CD-5253 (Box 100, Folder 3)
      - #17591. Spring Chickens II, 2010-2013 (Box 100, Folder 5)
        File number N 26/8/60
        Theater
        - Promotional DVD. Big Telly Theatre Company presents Spring Chickens - the Shows, 3rd October 2009, 2009-10-03; DVD-3453 (Box 100, Folder 5)
          File number N 26/8/60. Three copies of DVD.
      - #17591. Spring Chickens II. 2010-2011 interim report, 2010-2013 (Box 100, Folder 6)
        - Appendix E: Two Spring Chickens: Unlimited flights of imaginationâ¦Destination Utopia. 5 venues - 5 nights - 5 live shows, DVD-3454 (Box 100, Folder 6)
          File number N 26/8/60. DVD found in Appendix E.
    - Boston University, 1993-1995
      Boston University
      - #7245 (#94-15). Reaching Common Ground conference, 1993-1995 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Brendan Murtagh, 2009, 2011; Murtagh, Brendan
      Murtagh, Brendan
      Strategic Learning and Evaluation (Legacy)
      - #18041. Cluster evaluation - Aging Program Northern Ireland, 2009, 2011 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - British Irish Rights Watch, 1995-2011, 2013
      British Irish Rights Watch
      - British Irish Rights Watch (BIRW), 1995-1999 (Box 100, Folder 9-10)
        File number N 16/9a. No grant-related documents.
      - #7377 (#96-7); #7732 (#98-102); #8277; #8543. Core support, 2000-2001 (Box 100, Folder 11)
      - #7656 (#98-24). Bloody Sunday Trust, 1998-2001 (Box 100, Folder 12)
        File number N 16/9/1a